[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Have you ever thought you were going to be world famous for cross dressing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "No, never -- never in a million years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Are you nervous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "He had been abused?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Oh, abused his entire life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 76, "question": "How did you find this out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "So, he told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "You support him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he -- he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "No, I never felt that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "-- so that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["four years ago"]}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I did, about four years ago, I asked, why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Is he proud of you, for what you've achieved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I think so, because he -- in any situation, he's in tears.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is that guilt, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Listen, that's exactly what I thought very early on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "No, he hasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Would you like him to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Jaguar"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "How you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "The same as you come before me more than you go to the doctor, for a checkup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "You don't know me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Did you ever think, when you were young and you -- you thought of treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross dressing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Yes, never --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "It's about strong women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Any comment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "-- show off about it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Well, because it's -- I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "My faith.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "And I say no, but it's a very particular pressure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I actually did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Goldstein"]}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "How did you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Mostly I worked with the trainers, Anthony Goldstein (ph), a great guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Because there are --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Once, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "And what went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I think we were both very young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "It -- was it, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 510, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes, because we both were in a place where -- and I just realized I should not have said this, because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Because I said too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", ":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Why don't you ask another question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "It's a fascinating side to you, because you're being so nice about it and -- and so honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "And what's the rush?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "But don't you want little Tylers running around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yes, I want that more than I want to be married, though.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Should we move on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Yes, please.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Do you want have a glass of water?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "No, it's all good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "-- were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "No, no, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Did you have any idea who she was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "To be honest with you, I did not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "You'd never heard of her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I -- I had heard of her, but I didn't know all of -- that she had done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "You supplied the plane, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 751, "question": "The first black Bond?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "No, no, I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Smith"]}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "You reckon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Will Smith should be the first black Bond.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Why should it be him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Because -- because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "If you lose weight at the rate you're going, you'll be skinnier than Will Smith, no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Will Smith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "-- to give you, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "There is one moment I'll -- I'll -- and I'll probably regret it for my entire life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "How have you been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "I've been great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 853, "question": "-- for years, and it really dragged you down, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 854, "answer": "It really did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "When times were really tough, when you were going through that hellish period, maybe doubting if you'd ever come back from it, what did you mother say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "She told me to remember who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "But do you ever stop and think wow, I'm still only 33 and yet I've had this 18-year career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "It's pretty unbelievable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What's being a mother like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "Oh my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 949, "question": "Or had she just got lost in the maelstrom of fame and abuse and all the rest of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 950, "answer": "One of the things that I can't -- I can't put my mind around is where she really was because, you know, at the end of her life, I wasn't there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 956, "question": "As somebody who still can, do you understand what that feeling must be like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "MD", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBG", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 957, "answer": "Oh, my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 970, "question": "How did you hear it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 971, "answer": "I was actually in the same hotel that she passed in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 972, "question": "At the Beverly Hilton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 973, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Beverly Hilton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 985, "question": "It hit you that bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 986, "answer": "It hit me -- it just hit me in ways I can't even explain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 998, "question": "Are you excited about having a new album out now, with everything that you've been through in the last 10 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 999, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 1005, "question": "When you sing, what do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1006, "answer": "I feel everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1013, "question": "And how's your love life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1014, "answer": "Oh, my love life is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1022, "question": "Where did you meet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1023, "answer": "We met at a studio, at a studio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1025, "question": "On this is the one you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1026, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1031, "question": "RANDY: That's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1032, "answer": "That's it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 1034, "question": "Is there anything else you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1035, "answer": "Let me see --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 1036, "question": "Want to talk about world affairs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1037, "answer": "No, we covered everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]